<?xml version="1.0" encoding="Windows-1252" ?>
<XML_DIZ_INFO>
<MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
    <MASTER_PAD_VERSION>1.15</MASTER_PAD_VERSION>
    <MASTER_PAD_INFO>Portable Application Description, or PAD for short, is a data set that is used by shareware authors to disseminate information to anyone interested in their software products. To find out more go to http://www.asp-shareware.org/pad</MASTER_PAD_INFO>
</MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
<Company_Info>
        <Company_Name>Wilhelm Kurz</Company_Name>
        <Address_1>Zenettistrasse 41</Address_1>
        <Address_2 />
        <City_Town>Munich</City_Town>
        <State_Province />
        <Zip_Postal_Code>D-80337</Zip_Postal_Code>
        <Country>Germany</Country>
        <Company_WebSite_URL>http://www.wilhelm-kurz-software.de</Company_WebSite_URL>
<Contact_Info>
        <Author_First_Name>Wilhelm</Author_First_Name>
        <Author_Last_Name>Kurz</Author_Last_Name>
        <Author_Email>info@wilhelm-kurz-software.de</Author_Email>
        <Contact_First_Name>Wilhelm</Contact_First_Name>
        <Contact_Last_Name>Kurz</Contact_Last_Name>
        <Contact_Email>info@wilhelm-kurz-software.de</Contact_Email>
    </Contact_Info>
<Support_Info>
        <Sales_Email>info@wilhelm-kurz-software.de</Sales_Email>
        <Support_Email>info@wilhelm-kurz-software.de</Support_Email>
        <General_Email>info@wilhelm-kurz-software.de</General_Email>
        <Sales_Phone>+49(89)777200</Sales_Phone>
        <Support_Phone>+49(89)777200</Support_Phone>
        <General_Phone>+49(89)777200</General_Phone>
        <Fax_Phone />
    </Support_Info>
</Company_Info>
<Program_Info>
        <Program_Name>DynaPlot</Program_Name>
        <Program_Version>3.0</Program_Version>
        <Program_Release_Month>08</Program_Release_Month>
        <Program_Release_Day>08</Program_Release_Day>
        <Program_Release_Year>2002</Program_Release_Year>
        <Program_Cost_Dollars>175</Program_Cost_Dollars>
        <Program_Cost_Other_Code />
        <Program_Cost_Other />
        <Program_Type>Shareware</Program_Type>
        <Program_Release_Status>New Release</Program_Release_Status>
        <Program_Install_Support>Install and Uninstall</Program_Install_Support>
        <Program_OS_Support>Win95,Win98,WinME,WinNT 4.x,WinXP,Windows2000</Program_OS_Support>
        <Program_Language>English</Program_Language>
<File_Info>
        <Filename_Versioned>dynap300.zip</Filename_Versioned>
        <Filename_Previous />
        <Filename_Generic>dynaplot.zip</Filename_Generic>
        <Filename_Long>dynaplot.zip</Filename_Long>
        <File_Size_Bytes>2108283</File_Size_Bytes>
        <File_Size_K>2059</File_Size_K>
        <File_Size_MB>2.06</File_Size_MB>
    </File_Info>
<Expire_Info>
        <Has_Expire_Info>Y</Has_Expire_Info>
        <Expire_Count>60</Expire_Count>
        <Expire_Based_On>Days</Expire_Based_On>
        <Expire_Other_Info />
        <Expire_Month />
        <Expire_Day />
        <Expire_Year />
    </Expire_Info>
        <Program_Change_Info />
        <Program_Specific_Category>Development Tools</Program_Specific_Category>
        <Program_Categories>ActiveX, Charting, VB Components</Program_Categories>
        <Program_System_Requirements>MFC 4.2 DLLs</Program_System_Requirements>
        <Includes_JAVA_VM>N</Includes_JAVA_VM>
        <Includes_VB_Runtime>N</Includes_VB_Runtime>
        <Includes_DirectX>N</Includes_DirectX>
</Program_Info>
<Program_Descriptions>
<English>
        <Keywords>ActiveX, chart, control, plot, visualization, tolerance, curve</Keywords>
        <Char_Desc_45>ActiveX chart for technical applications</Char_Desc_45>
        <Char_Desc_80>Real-time ActiveX chart control with built-in tools for technical applications</Char_Desc_80>
        <Char_Desc_250>DynaPlot is a real-time ActiveX chart control for technical  applications. It features dynamic scaling of chart elements with control size, tolerance masks, built-in tools like cursors, markers, scroll, pan, zoom...</Char_Desc_250>
        <Char_Desc_450>DynaPlot is a real-time chart control for technical and scientific applications. It features dynamic scaling of chart elements with control size, tolerance masks, built-in tools like cursors, markers, scroll, pan, zoom... Although flexible and comprehensive, DynaPlot's programming interface is easy to learn which makes it the tool of choice for both T+M and rapid application development. Examples in VB, VC, VB.NET,C#... help you to get started.</Char_Desc_450>
        <Char_Desc_2000>DynaPlot is a real-time chart control for technical and scientific applications. It features dynamic scaling of chart elements with control size, tolerance masks, built-in tools like cursors, markers, scroll, pan, zoom... Although flexible and comprehensive, DynaPlot's programming interface is easy to learn which makes it the tool of choice for both T+M and rapid application development. Examples in VB, VC, VB.NET,C#... help you to get started.</Char_Desc_2000>
</English>
</Program_Descriptions>
<Web_Info>
<Application_URLs>
        <Application_Info_URL>http://www.wilhelm-kurz-software.de/dynaplot/dynaplot.htm</Application_Info_URL>
        <Application_Order_URL>http://www.wilhelm-kurz-software.de/dynaplot/order.htm</Application_Order_URL>
        <Application_Screenshot_URL>http://www.wilhelm-kurz-software.de/dynaplot/tol.gif</Application_Screenshot_URL>
        <Application_Icon_URL>http://www.wilhelm-kurz-software.de/dynaplot/icon.gif</Application_Icon_URL>
        <Application_XML_File_URL>http://www.wilhelm-kurz-software.de/dynaplot/pad_file.xml</Application_XML_File_URL>
    </Application_URLs>
<Download_URLs>
        <Primary_Download_URL>http://www.wilhelm-kurz-software.de/dynaplot/dynaplot.zip</Primary_Download_URL>
        <Secondary_Download_URL />
        <Additional_Download_URL_1 />
        <Additional_Download_URL_2 />
    </Download_URLs>
</Web_Info>
<Permissions>
        <Distribution_Permissions>DynaPlot is distributed as &quot;shareware&quot;.  You
may freely copy and distribute the DynaPlot DISTRIBUTION FILE 
in unmodified form.  However, it is prohibited to modify the
DISTRIBUTION FILE or to distribute any components extracted
from it.</Distribution_Permissions>
        <EULA>DynaPlot GENERAL LICENSE AGREEMENT

NOTICE: BY INSTALLING AND USING DynaPlot YOU ARE AGREEING TO BE
BOUND BY THE TERMS OF THIS AGREEMENT. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE
TERMS OF THIS AGREEMENT, PROMPTLY DELETE ALL DynaPlot FILES FROM
YOUR COMPUTER.

1) OWNER: The manufacturer of this software and the owner of all
associated copyrights is Wilhelm Kurz of Zenettistrasse 41, 
D-80337 Munich, Germany (&quot;The Author&quot;). 

2) APPLICABILITY: This AGREEMENT is a GENERAL LICENSE AGREEMENT
which applies to all users of DynaPlot. If you have other
licensing agreements with The Author for the use of DynaPlot, 
terms of this agreement which are not specifically addressed 
in those agreements shall be considered amendments to those agreements.

3) AS IS: DynaPlot, WHETHER OR NOT REGISTERED, IS PROVIDED &quot;AS
IS&quot; WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND. The Author
DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EITHER EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF
MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND
NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL The Author
OR HIS SUPPLIERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES
WHATSOEVER (INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF
BUSINESS PROFITS, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, LOSS OF BUSINESS
INFORMATION, OR OTHER PECUNIARY LOSS) ARISING OUT OF THE USE
OF OR INABILITY TO USE ANY DynaPlot SOFTWARE, EVEN IF The Author
HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY
OF SUCH DAMAGES.  BECAUSE SOME STATES DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION
OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL
DAMAGES, THE ABOVE LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.

4) DISTRIBUTION: DynaPlot is distributed as &quot;shareware&quot;.  You
may freely copy and distribute the DynaPlot DISTRIBUTION FILE 
in unmodified form.  However, it is prohibited to modify the
DISTRIBUTION FILE or to distribute any components extracted
from it. 

5) LICENSE TYPES:
DynaPlot is available as Professional Version, Student Version, 
OEM User License, OEM Manufacturer License, Site License and 
Global License.

DynaPlot Student Version has restricted functionality and is for 
private, educational purposes only. 

DynaPlot Professional Version grants you the right to install 
DynaPlot on one computer. You may manufacture and distribute applications 
developed with DynaPlot Professional Version free of royalties.

A DynaPlot OEM Manufacturer License grants you the right to pass on 
the OEM USER REGISTRATION KEY provided to you by the Author to Users
of your products which include DynaPlot as a component. By receving 
the OEM USER REGISTRATION KEY a user (&quot;User&quot;) is granted a DynaPlot 
OEM User License. A DynaPlot OEM Manufacturer may distribute free trial 
versions of his product but will charge a nonegligible price for the 
final product to prevent uncontrolled distribution of free DynaPlot 
OEM User Licenses.

A DynaPlot OEM User License grants you the right to manufacture and 
distribute applications which include DynaPlot if and only if the 
OEM Manufacturer's control or application is also used in and shipped
with these applications.

A DynaPlot Site License extends DynaPlot Professional Version by the 
right to install DynaPlot on any number of computers at one company site.

A DynaPlot Global License extends DynaPlot Professional Version by the 
right to install DynaPlot on any number of computers world wide.
 
6) TRIAL PERIOD:  When you install the DynaPlot program by
extracting files from the DISTRIBUTION FILE and copying them to
a given computer, a trial period of 60 days begins.  DynaPlot
may be used freely for 60 days operating in an &quot;unregistered&quot;
mode.  If you do not register DynaPlot, you agree to remove the
DynaPlot extraction files from the computer within 60 days after
installation.  DynaPlot will stop functioning at the end of its
trial period.

7) REGISTRATION: REGISTRATION is the process by which you gain
full license to use DynaPlot.  REGISTRATION is initiated when you
provide a suggested REGISTRATION NAME, an e-mail and/or postal
address, and the required registration fee, if any, to The Author.
Upon receipt of your registration information and fee, The Author will
send you return registration information consisting of your
official REGISTRATION NAME, the corresponding UNLOCK KEY NUMBER 
and the serial number of DynaPlot to which your REGISTRATION
applies. The Author may assign a REGISTRATION NAME other than what
you suggest.  Your receipt of this information completes REGISTRATION, 
which licenses you to use applicable version(s) of DynaPlot indefinitely. 
You are licensed to use any past, present or future version of DynaPlot 
which accepts your REGISTRATION NAME and UNLOCK KEY NUMBER.  

8) ROYALTIES: DynaPlot is royalty-free. Applications created with 
DynaPlot may be sold freely. Applications created with unregistered 
versions of DynaPlot or with DynaPlot Student Version may not be sold.

9) REGISTRATION KEY NUMBER USAGE: You agree not to disclose your
confidential REGISTRATION KEY NUMBER to any third party. Holders of 
a DynaPlot OEM Manufacturer License may distribute the 
OEM USER REGISTRATION KEY provided to them by The Autor to users of
their products which include DynaPlot as a component. 
A single registration may be used only on a single computer; you must
purchase multiple REGISTRATIONS or a DynaPlot Site License or 
DynaPlot Global License to use DynaPlot on multiple computers. 
Your REGISTRATION may be transferred to a another computer owned 
by you simply by installing the DynaPlot files on the new computer
and deleting them from the previous computer; however, because 
the REGISTRATION process gives you knowledge of the confidential 
REGISTRATION KEY NUMBER, your REGISTRATION is not transferable to 
a third party.

10) FREE REGISTRATION: The Author may grant FREE REGISTRATIONS 
for promotional purposes.  If The Author has granted you 
FREE REGISTRATION, it does not imply, acknowledge, or grant any 
ownership or other rights whatsoever to DynaPlot beyond that of 
REGISTRATION, as described above.

11) GOVERNING LAW :Any action related to this License will be governed 
by German law. No choice of law rules of any jurisdiction will apply.</EULA>
</Permissions>
<Simtel>
    <Simtel_Agent />
    <Simtel_FORM>Y</Simtel_FORM>
    <Simtel_DOS_Category>Select - MS-DOS Platform (blank)</Simtel_DOS_Category>
    <Simtel_Platform>win95 - Win95/Win98/WinME</Simtel_Platform>
    <Simtel_Category>Programming - visbasic Visual Basic Programming Language</Simtel_Category>
    <SIMTEL_FORM_VER>1.3 8/01/2002</SIMTEL_FORM_VER>
</Simtel>
</XML_DIZ_INFO>
